Guide to the Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records, 1940s-2002 RG.3.J
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Processed, 1971-1981; 54.0 Cubic feet; (45) cartons
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Physically Handicapped: ACCESS Modifications for, 1975-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 30)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: "A Position on the Adequacy of the Subsidy Model", 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 31)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Projected Characteristics of OSU: 1974-1990, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 32)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Proposal for an Extended Learning Program, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 33)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Proposal for Small Business Development Center (SBDC), 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 34)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: A Proposed Method for Gathering Financial Information About Private Institutions, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 35)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Proposed New Expenditure Models, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 36)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Regional Campus Development Instruction, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 37)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Report on Regional Campus Nursing, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 38)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: "Role in Coordination and Management of the Educational Enterprise", 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 39)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: State General and Technical Colleges: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0029, Folder 40)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: State Federal and Technical Colleges: Creation of, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 1)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Study of Enrollments in Remedial English and Mathematics, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 2)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Subsidy Formula Revision, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 3)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Subsidy Model: Position on:, 1973 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 4)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Substitute House Bill 301: Correspondence and Reports, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 5)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Task Force on Higher Education: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 6)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Task Force on Higher Education: Regional Assembly, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 7)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Task Force on Higher Education: Reports, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 8)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: Transplex/OSU: Building Program, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 9)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: 1202 Advisory Committee, 1974-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 10)
  - Ohio Board of Regents: A Working Paper on the Adequacy of the Regents' Subsidy Model, 1973 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 11)
  - Ohio Coal Research Laboratories Association, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 12)
  - Ohio College Association: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 13)
  - Ohio College Association: Memorandums, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 14)
  - Ohio College Association: Minutes, 1975-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 15)
  - Ohio Council on Economic Education: Correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 16)
  - Ohio Council on Economic Education: Executive Committee: Minutes, 1970-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 17)
  - Ohio Council on Economic Education: Report: Round-Up, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 18)
  - Ohio Council on Economic Education: Report: Summary, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 19)
  - Ohio Ethics Commission, 1974-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 20)
  - Ohio General Assembly: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 21)
  - Ohio General Assembly: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 22)
  - Ohio General Assembly: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 23)
  - Ohio General Assembly: Public Budget Hearings: Testimony, 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 24)
  - Ohio Highway Transportation Research Center, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 25)
  - Ohio Legal Center Institute (Law School): Annual Report, 1971 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 26)
  - Ohio Legislative Reports, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 27)
  - Ohio Legislative Reports, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 28)
  - Ohio Legislative Reports, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 29)
  - Ohio Legislative Reports, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 30)
  - Ohio Legislative Reports, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0030, Folder 31)
  - Ohio Legislative Reports, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 1)
  - Ohio Public Interest Research Group (OPIRG): Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 2)
  - Ohio State University Poll: Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 3)
  - OSU Polls and Centennial Commission: University and Society: Alumni and Citizen Views by Patrick Cotter: OSUP: Director of Information and Analysis, undated (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 4)
  - OSU Student and Faculty Polls: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 5)
  - Olentangy Freeway: Correspondence, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 6)
  - Ombudsman: Office of: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 7)
  - Ombudsman: Office of: Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 8)
  - Ombudsman: Office of: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 9)
  - Ombudsman: Office of: Nominations, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 10)
  - Ombudsman: Office of: Search Committee, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 11)
  - Ombudsman: Office of: Second Annual Report, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 12)
  - Ombudsman: Office of: Survey of Client Evaluation, Fall 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 13)
  - Ombudsman: Office of: Third Annual Report, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 14)
  - Optometry: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 15)
  - Optometry: College of: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 16)
  - Optometry: College of: Project: File Documents, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 17)
  - Optometry: College of: Report of the Evaluation Team, 1972 November 13-16 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 18)
  - Orientation and Testing Center: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 19)
  - Orton Foundation: Minutes and Reports, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 20)
  - Orton Foundation: Minutes and Reports, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 21)
  - Orton Foundation: Minutes and Reports, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 22)
  - Orton Foundation: Minutes and Reports, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 23)
  - Orton Foundation: Minutes and Reports, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 24)
  - Orton Foundation: Minutes and Reports, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 25)
  - Orton Foundation: Minutes and Reports, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 26)
  - Owens, Jesse: Dedications of Track and Recreation Facilities: Correspondence, 1980 March-October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 27)
  - Owens, Jesse: Football Program for Track Dedication, 1980 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 28)
  - Owens, Jesse. Memorial Foundation Fund, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 29)
  - Owens, Jesse: OSU Monthly Article, 1980 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 30)
  - Owens, Jesse: OSU Quest Article, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 31)
  - Owens, Jesse: Track: Plans and Drawings, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0031, Folder 32)
  - Patent Advisory Committee, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 1)
  - Perkins Observatory, 1973-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 2)
  - Personal Information Systems, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 3)
  - Personnel: Office of: Memos, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Data Records: Comparative Salary Analysis: OSU, Michigan, Illinois, Minnesota, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 5)
  - Personnel Services: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 6)
  - Personnel Services: Executive Director of: Collective Bargaining, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 7)
  - Personnel Services: Executive Director of: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 8)
  - Personnel Services: Executive Director of: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 9)
  - Personnel Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence (Incl. Reports, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 10)
  - Personnel Services: Vice-President for: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0032, Folder 11)
  - Pharmacy: College of, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 1)
  - Phi Kappa Phi: Petition for Establishment of a Chapter, 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 2)
  - Phoenix International Corp: Project Enterprise, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 3)
  - Physical Education: School of, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 4)
  - Physical Plant: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 5)
  - Physically Impaired: Office of, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 6)
  - Physically Impaired: Office of: 504 Self-Evaluation, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 7)
  - Physically Impaired: Office of: Report from the Task Force on the Physically Impaired, 1974 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 8)
  - Police Salaries: Job Descriptions, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 9)
  - Policy Review: Committee on: Subsidy Formula Revision, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 10)
  - President's Club: Correspondence and Reports, 1971-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 11)
  - President's Club: Correspondence and Reports, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 12)
  - President's Club: Correspondence and Reports, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 13)
  - President's Special Assistant: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 14)
  - President's Special Assistant: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 15)
  - President's Staff Meetings: Agenda and Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 16)
  - President's Staff Meetings: Agenda and Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 17)
  - President's Staff Meetings: Agenda and Minutes, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 18)
  - President's Staff Meetings: Memorandum, 1975-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 19)
  - Program 60: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 20)
  - Program 60: Senior Career Study Placement Program: Proposal, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 21)
  - Program 60: By-Laws, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 22)
  - Program 60: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0033, Folder 23)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Blacks: OSU Attitude Toward, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 1)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Candidates for Vice-President of, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 2)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Correspondence, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 3)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Correspondence, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 4)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Correspondence, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 5)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Correspondence, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 6)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Correspondence, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 7)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 8)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Honors Information Project, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 9)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Leslie, John W.: Vice-Presidential Candidate, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 10)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Ohio Opinion Leaders Survey: Final and Summary Report, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 11)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Organization and Functions, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 12)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Position Description for Vice-President, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 13)
  - Public Affairs: Office of: Shea, James W.: Vice-Presidential Candidate, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 14)
  - Public Safety: Director of: Annual Reports, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 15)
  - Public Safety: Director of: Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 16)
  - Public Safety: Director of: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 17)
  - Public Safety: Director of: Report: Inadequacy, Instability and Poor Morale: A Study in Fact, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0034, Folder 18)
  - Questionnaires, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 1)
  - Questionnaires, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaires, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate and Land Acquisition, 1973 January-February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 4)
  - Regional Campuses: Citizens Advisory Committee Conference, 1971-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 5)
  - Regional Campuses: Communications Project: Summary Report, 1974 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 6)
  - Regional Campuses: Freshman Foundation Program: Summary of Info, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 7)
  - Regional Campuses: Freshman Foundation Program and the Developmental Education Program: Report, 1976 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 8)
  - Regional Campuses: Lima Branch, 1971-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 9)
  - Regional Campuses: Lima Branch: Barnes-Nieswander Associates Employment:, undated (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 10)
  - Regional Campuses: Mansfield Branch, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 11)
  - Regional Campuses: Mansfield Branch, 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 12)
  - Regional Campuses: Marion Branch, 1971-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 13)
  - Regional Campuses: Marion Branch, 1975-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 14)
  - Regional Campuses: Marion Branch: Relationship with Marion Technical College, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 15)
  - Regional Campuses: Newark Branch, 1972-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 16)
  - Regional Campuses: Newark Branch, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 17)
  - Regional Campuses: Reference Material for Panel Review, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 18)
  - Regional Campuses: Resident Credit Center Planning Report and Application for Subsidy, undated (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 19)
  - Regional Campuses: Vice-President for: Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 20)
  - Regional Campuses: Vice-President for: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 21)
  - Regional Campuses: Vice-President for: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 22)
  - Registration Services: Office of: Statistical Summary, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0035, Folder 23)
  - Registrar: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 1)
  - Registrar: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 2)
  - Registrar: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 3)
  - Registrar: University and Government Relations, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 4)
  - Religious Affairs, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 5)
  - Research Foundation: Office of, 1975-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 6)
  - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC): Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 7)
  - Research Foundation: Office of: Research and Sponsored Programs, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 8)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Budget and Proposed Rates, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 9)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Committee to Review The Ohio State University Residence Hall Judicial System, 1979 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 10)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Correspondence, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 11)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 12)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 13)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 14)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Dormitory Revenue Bond Funds, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 15)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Installation of Smoke Detectors, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 16)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Search Committee: Director of, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 17)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Space Utlizations and Fiscal Plans, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 18)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: Student Apartment Service (SAS), 1970 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 19)
  - Residence and Dining Halls: Office of: University Government Relations, 1974-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 20)
  - Resource Planning: Advisory Committee on: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 21)
  - Resource Planning: Advisory Committee on: Final Report, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 22)
  - Resource Planning and Priorities Committee, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 23)
  - Resource Planning and Priorities Committee, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 24)
  - Rhodes Scholarships, 1975 August-September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 25)
  - Scholarship Recognition Dinner: Correspondence and Agendas, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 26)
  - Senior Citizens Auditing Program, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 27)
  - Senior Class Committee: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 28)
  - Sexual Harassment: Correspondence, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 29)
  - Sloan, Alfred P. Foundation: News Release, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 30)
  - Social and Behavioral Sciences: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 31)
  - Social Work: College of: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 32)
  - Social Work: School of: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 33)
  - South African Investments: Correspondence, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 34)
  - Space: Leased by OSU: Summary of, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 35)
  - Speech and Hearing: Dept. of, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0036, Folder 36)
  - Commencement Address Kent State University: "Tinkering with University Government", 1972 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 1)
  - Greetings and Welcome to Medical Alumni (Document Missing), 1972 Spetember (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Club Officers Conference, 1972 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 3)
  - Ohio Dental Association: Dentistry, The Public Health, and Professional Education in Education in the Health Services--Notes from an Overstuffed Briefcase, 1972 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 4)
  - Tape for Broadcast on WOSU-TV, 1972 September 27 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 5)
  - Address to Freshmen, 1972 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 6)
  - Statement to The Ohio State University, 1972 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 7)
  - Letter to Students, Faculty and Staff Re Issue No. 2, 1972 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 8)
  - Address to Annual Extension Conference: "The Ohio State University and its Future-An Odyssey of Discovery", 1972 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 9)
  - Greetings to Personnel and Payroll Employees, 1972 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 10)
  - First Geo/Solid Earth and Ocean Physics Research Conference, 1972 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 11)
  - Report to Faculty, 1972 October 26 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 12)
  - Columbus Rotary Club, 1972 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 13)
  - Address to Kiwanis Club of Columbus, 1972 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 14)
  - Inaugural Address and Commencement: "To be United in Shared Purposes", 1972 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 15)
  - Misc. Statements, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 16)
  - "Women in Higher Education" to Columbus Chapter of American Association of University Women, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 17)
  - Open Letter to Faculty and Staff, 1972-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 18)
  - Ohio Newspaper Association Convention, 1973 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 19)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1973 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 20)
  - "Tinkering with University Government": Educational Record: Vol. 54, No. 1, 1973, 1973 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 21)
  - Misc Statements, 1973 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 22)
  - Women (Greek Letter) in Higher Education: To Delta Zeta Sorority: State Day, 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 23)
  - Statement Re Education to Junior League of Columbus, 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 24)
  - American Society of Public Administration, 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 25)
  - Erie County Alumni in Huron, Ohio (Document Missing), 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 26)
  - Washington Alumni Club, 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 27)
  - Testimony Before the Education Section, House of Representatives Appropriation Committee Re House Bill 86, 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Club-Hamilton County, 1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 29)
  - Statement Re Governor's New Proposal, 1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 30)
  - Cleveland OSU Alumni Club, 1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 31)
  - Pacesetters Banquet (Document Missing), 1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 32)
  - President's Club, 1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 33)
  - Public Relations Society of America: "Public Relations in a University", 1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 34)
  - Honor Medical Society, 1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 35)
  - Miami County Alumni in Troy, Ohio, 1973 April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 36)
  - Board of Trustees Faculty and Staff Dinner, 1973 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 37)
  - Alumni Club, Steubenville, Ohio, 1973 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 38)
  - Twentieth Annual Engineers and Architects Conference: "The University as A Large System" (Document Missing), 1973 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 39)
  - Senate Finance Committee Testimony, 1973 May 15 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 40)
  - Special Message for Agricultural Technical Institute: May 15, 1973 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 41)
  - Williams County Alumni Club, 1973 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 42)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1973 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 43)
  - Mahoning County Alumni at Youngstown, 1973 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 44)
  - OSU New York Alumni Club, 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 45)
  - University of New Mexico Commencement: "The Management 'Overkill' in Universities", 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 46)
  - Trends in Research Activity, 1973 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 47)
  - Lincoln Tower, 1973 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 48)
  - Lorrain County Alumni Club: "The Many Strengths of The Ohio State University", 1973 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 49)
  - Statement Delivered at ACE Meeting: "The Future Financing of Post-Secondary Education", 1973 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 50)
  - Lima Rotary Club, 1973 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 51)
  - Women's Day on Campus (Document Missing), 1973 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 52)
  - Comment on Fall Enrollment, 1973 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 53)
  - Ross County Alumni, 1973 November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 54)
  - Phi Kappa Phi: "The Confessions of a Sophomore President", 1973 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 55)
  - Ohio Common Pleas Judges Association, 1973 December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 56)
  - Article for Publication in the Lantern, 1974 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 57)
  - New York Times Editorial: "Twenty-five Hour Day is not Enough", 1974 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 58)
  - National Football Foundation Hall of Fame, 1974 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 59)
  - Delta Kappa: Columbus: "Reflections on the Intramural Confines of an Academic Administrative World", 1974 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 60)
  - Seminar on Low Tuition: Washington D.C, 1974 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 61)
  - Dinner Honoring Jerome Folkman (Document Missing), 1974 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 62)
  - Anonymously Yours Letter, 1974 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 63)
  - Rho Chi Society, 1974 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 64)
  - Financing of Higher Education Class, 1974 Febraury (Box UA.RG.3.J.0037, Folder 65)